

Emmanuel KWIZERA

Software Engineer

Am passionate developer with 3 years and 9 months of experience, in my daily work I use Laravel Framework, reactJS on front end side and Flutter on mobile development. I have been working in different companies as back end developer, other worked as full stack developer and current am software engineer at techaffinity inc, in this journey I gained more experiences and skills like providing RESTful APIs, micro services, git, database design and implementation, self learn, teamwork sprit and I enjoy to be a problems solver, etc.

\times

emmizokwizera@gmail.com



+250781167275



KK 440 st, Kigali, Rwanda

SKILLS

Laravel Framework

Flutter

Database(mySQL,Oracle)

React JS

PHP Programming languages

JavaScript,jQuery

Bootstrap

HTML,CSS

Git Version

RESTFul API

Swagger

Postman

Microservices

Basic Skills in Spring Framework

OS Platforms: windows, Linux OpenSUSE,MacOS

LANGUAGES

English
Professional Working Proficiency

Kinyarwanda *Native*

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software Engineer TechAffinity Inc

06/2021 - Present techaffinity.com

Duties

- Build back end using Laravel framework
- Build front end using ReactJS and Flutter
- Providing APIs using swagger or postman
- Analyse database and Implement it
- Working on WordPress Project
- Headless CMS with react
- using jQuery and JavaScript
- Trainee Interns
- Leading team of 15 Peoples

Full stack developer Nozaax Lab

11/2019 - 06/2021

Duties

 $\ ^{\square}$ -Build back end by providing APIs and front end using Laravel Blade

- -Use PHP programming, jQuery and JavaScript
- Participate in build e-commerce using WordPress woo-commerce
- Build front end with ReactJS
- Debugging

Backend Developer HviewTech Group Ltd Company

04/2019 - 11/2019

Using

PHP/Laravel Framework

CERTIFICATES

RESTful API with HTTP and JavaScript

Advanced Relational Database and SQL

Introduction to Front-end Development with ReactJS

EDUCATION

Full-time University of Kigali

09/2020 - 01/2022

Information Technology

Bachelor Degree in Information Technology

Kigali-Rwanda

Kigali-Rwanda

Kigali City -Rwanda

Kigali-City